thinkaction.com 2010-01-06

# ThinkAction - Leads Generation | Customer Acquisiton | Affiliate Network

**Think Action**™ recognizes the privacy concerns of visitors to its site on the Internet ([www.thinkaction.com](http://www.thinkaction.com/)). Specifically, ThinkAction recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about the visitors to the ThinkAction website. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or email address, is automatically collected when you visit the ThinkAction site. ThinkAction may collect certain non-personal information, which is used only to optimize ThinkAction Web pages for your computer (e.g., the identity of your Internet browser, the type of operating system you use, and the domain name of your Internet service provider). This non-personal information may also be used by ThinkAction to determine the total number of visitors to its website. Personally identifiable information about visitors to the ThinkAction site is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. In those instances when ThinkAction does collect such information, the following applies: How We Use Data Collected on This Site Except as described in this Privacy Policy, personally identifiable information that is submitted knowingly and voluntarily by visitors to the ThinkAction site is retained by ThinkAction and is not sold or otherwise transferred to an outside company, unless otherwise stated at the time of collection. 

Use of Cookies  
ThinkAction Online not use cookies to obtain any personal information about our users. 

Notice  
ThinkAction will notify you when it is collecting personally identifiable information about you, as well as the use or uses ThinkAction intends to make of such information. Information is used in aggregate. No personally identifiable information is reported or used. 

Explanation of Policy  
By using this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy of ThinkAction. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use this site. ThinkAction reviews its Privacy Policy periodically and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this Policy at anytime. This page should be reviewed from time to time so that you are updated on any changes.

Other Sites  
ThinkActions operates different web sites under different domain names. These sites are identified as " **Powered By ThinkActio** n" When you visit a site " **Powered By ThinkAction** " please be sure to read the privacy policy associate with that site.
